wetset.net 2019-07-15

# Wet Set - Panty Wetting, Panty Pooping, Adult Babies, Diaper Lovers - Privacy Policy

Privacy Declaration

Redrose BV – 21-5-2018

**General**

We are aware that you need to have confidence in us. We therefore see it as our responsibility to protect your privacy. In this privacy statement, we will let you know, among other things, what information we collect and why we collect this data.

This privacy statement applies to the services of Redrose B.V. (Redrose). By using this website you accept our privacy policy.

**Personal data**

Personal data is data that can be used to identify your identity.

When you create an account on one of our websites, we ask you to provide your e-mail. This e-mail address is only used to create or restore an account for you. The legal basis for processing this personal data is that the processing is performed on the basis of an agreement. If you register for our newsletter, we will ask for your e-mail address. In this case, we only use your e-mail to send the newsletter. We then process your e-mail on the basis of the customer's permission.

If you make a purchase, your name and bank details are also necessary. This data is only used to process your purchase. The legal basis for processing this personal data is that the processing is performed on the basis of an agreement. The IP address of all website visitors is also processed for security reasons. IP addresses are only used to prevent fraud. IP addresses are stored in a hashed format. This means that a new code is immediately created from the IP address. This ensures the security of your IP address. We process your IP address on the basis of the customer's permission.

In addition, we can process your website behavior through Google Analytics. We do this to optimize our websites. We process this data only on the basis of the customer's permission.

The data is stored on Redrose's own secure servers or those of a third party. We will not combine this information with other personal information we have.

You are not obliged to release your personal data, but we would like to point out that the provision of certain services becomes impossible when you refuse the processing of personal data.

**Communication**

When you send e-mail or other messages to us, we may keep those messages. This makes it possible to process your questions and answer your requests. The data is stored on secure servers or those of a third party. We will not combine this information with other personal information we have.

**Purposes of data processing**

The personal data that we process from you are only used for the following purposes:

\- to create an account for you  
\- to be able to contact you  
\- sending newsletters, promotions and promotions based on your explicit prior consent **[1]**  
\- website optimization  
\- the delivery and invoicing of products or services ordered by you  

We do not collect or use information for purposes other than the purposes described in this privacy statement, unless we have obtained your consent in advance.

**1** If you are already included in our mailing list for receiving marketing material, your data may be used by us for sending marketing, products and / or services. You can withdraw this permission at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each promotional e-mail message.

**Duration of processing**

Your personal data is stored and processed by us for a period that is necessary for the purpose of the processing, which may be related to the nature of our relationship to you.

**Your rights as a data subject**

The privacy legislation gives you a number of rights. We are happy to inform you about this. You can exercise your rights by contacting us via the e-mail address displayed on this website or via the contact form.

**Right of access and inspection:**

You have the right to request free access to your personal data at any time and the use we make of your personal data.

**Right of improvement, deletion and limitation:**

You always have the right to ask us to correct, supplement or delete your personal data. You may also request to limit the processing of your personal data. However, it is important to realize that with a request for the removal of your personal data, certain services and / or products can no longer be delivered.

**Right of objection:**

The privacy legislation gives you the right of objection against the processing of your personal data for serious and legitimate reasons. In addition, you always have the right to oppose the use of personal data for direct marketing purposes; you do not need to state any reasons for this.

**Right of data transfer:**

You have the right to obtain your Personal Data in a normal and readable form and / or to transfer it to other responsible persons.

**Right of withdrawal of your permission:**

Insofar as the processing is based on your prior consent, you have the right to withdraw that permission.

**Right to complain:**

If you have a complaint about privacy violation, we would like to hear from you. We try to find a solution with you as quickly and as well as possible. If you are dissatisfied, please contact us by telephone or in writing. You also have the right to file a complaint with the Dutch Data Protection Authority, established in The Hague.

**Share data with others?**

Your personal data will not be shared with third parties without your consent. Should this be necessary or desirable, we will ask you for permission to forward your data to other companies or bodies. When passing on your data to third parties, we will do everything we can to ensure an equivalent level of protection, for example by having our contract partners sign confidentiality statements in line with the content of this privacy statement.

In rare cases, we may have to release your personal data without your permission, for example on the basis of a court order or to comply with other mandatory laws and regulations. Redrose will make reasonable efforts to inform you in advance.

The internal processing of your data is done by employees who are obliged to confidentiality and confidentiality.

**Liability:**

We have taken security measures to protect your personal data, such that these measures are reasonable in relation to the risk of loss or falsification of personal data. Should a situation arise in which your data are processed in an unauthorized manner or by unauthorized persons, we would like to hear it as soon as possible so that we can take measures and limit damage.

In no event can Redrose be held liable for damages (direct or indirect) resulting from incorrect or unlawful use by a third party of your personal data.

You must always comply with the safety regulations for the protection of your own equipment and internet connection, among other things by preventing any unauthorized access to your login. You are and remain responsible for the use of your computer, IP address and identification data, and also for the confidentiality thereof.

**Changes:**

This privacy statement is tailored to the services of Redrose. Any adjustments and/or changes to our services may result in changes to this privacy statement. It is therefore advisable to consult this privacy statement on a regular basis and if you have questions about your privacy you can always contact us.

**Questions and feedback:**

We regularly check whether we comply with this privacy statement. If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, please contact us: 

**Redrose BV  
Nieuwe hemweg 4 hal c.  
1013BG, Amsterdam  
Netherlands**
